# Piotr Purzycki

### Wordpress (+Vue.jS) Front-end Developer



Date of birth: January 18, 1981

Address: Krotoszyńska 65a 51-009 Wrocław, Poland https://www.linkedin.com/in/piotr-purzycki/

phone: (+48) 609 732 132 mail: piotr@purzycki.pl https://github.com/purzykhttps://purzycki.pl/

#### About me

Self-motivated developer with 10+ years of experiance in developing Wordpress Websites.

Currently intrested in learning and working with JavaScript, preferably VUE.js Experience in coding pixel perfect and in the SEO/SEM area.

Hobbies: squash and playing drums. Married with two children.

# Technologies / tools

VUE.js, Nuxt.js, Tailwind, HTML, CSS, PHP, Dot.net, Twig/Timber, ACF Pro, SCSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Webpack, Git, Adobe XD, Figma,, Photoshop, Zeplin, Jira, Slack, Vistual Studio Code, Wordpress, Kentico, Umbraco

#### **Work Experience**

#### ADHD Interactive / Front-end Kentico & Umbraco Developer

January 2022 - January 2023

https://adhdinteractive.com/

Developing front-end for .net core websites - mainly Umbraco and Kentico CMSes.

#### eFresh / Wordpress Full Stack Developer

May 2020 - December 2021

https://www.efresh.com.pl/

Developing Wordpress websites, SEO and SEM optimalizations.

#### Mobile Five Media Ltd / Wordpress Front-end Developer

May 2019 - May 2020

https://hyd.agency/

Wordpress Front-end coding for one of the largest interactive agencies in Great Britain.

#### Piotr Purzycki / Wordpress Full Stack Developer

September 2009 - March 2019

Coding Wordpress themes, WooCommerce implementation, ad hoc customer assistance, SEO and SEM optimalizations.

#### **Education**

#### **Wroclaw University of Science and Technology**

Faculty of Information and Technology / Part time studies

\_\_

#### **Portfolio**

## Purzycki – Portfolio website | Next.js and Contentful CMS

January 2023

https://purzycki.pl/

https://github.com/purzyk/purzycki-portfolio

Build width React Next.js and Tailwind Filtering based on contentful categories

#### Vue.js - Headless Wordpress SPA

December 2022

https://wordpress-vue-headless.netlify.app/ https://github.com/purzyk/wordpress-vue-headless

Build for learning puproses with VUE.js Based on a website, that i made for a client. (https://stahlconst.eu/en/). Data feched form Wordpress Rest API. Form validate with Vee-Validate.

#### **GBGB - Wordpress Website**

Ma 2022

https://www.gbgb.org.uk/

Wordpress Website for the British dog racing federation. Data fetched via API and displayed on the website with VueJS.

#### Pokedex - Vue.js app for Pokemon

December 2022

https://purzycki-pokedex.netlify.app/ https://github.com/purzyk/pokedex-vue

Build for learning puproses.

Made with Vue.js and Tailwind – data fetched from free Pokemon API.

Autocomplete, add to favourites, load more on scroll.

#### Nuxt.js + Tailwind ecommerce website

December 2022

https://ecommerce-nuxt-pinia.netlify.app/, https://github.com/purzyk/ecommerce-nuxt-pinia

Build for learning puproses.

Made with Nuxt.js, Tailwind, Pinia - data fetched from dummy json.

Form validation with Vee-Validate. Product filters based on price and category.

#### Port Praski - Wordpress website

October 2021

https://portpraski.pl/en/

Wordpress Website for a Warsaw residental developer.

In the apartments section data filtered with VUE.js.

https://portpraski.pl/en/znajdz-lokal/